https://www.layermarneytower.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Search:
FacebookTwitterPinterestInstagramYouTube
Weddings CorporateCorporate Venue LocationsCorsellis Room Long Gallery Map and Linen Rooms Grounds
Planning Your Corporate EventCorporate Event Catering Corporate Event Entertainment in Essex Corporate Event Glamping Corporate Event Transportation
EducationEducational Visits Essex Planning Your Educational Visit Testimonials
VisitingEvents Tower and GroundsTower Testimonials
Planning Your Visit Guided ToursTestimonials
Visiting as a Group
PartiesParty Venue LocationsCorsellis Room Long Gallery Grounds
Planning Your Party
Glamping Tymperleys News About Contact
Privacy Policy
Please read the following Privacy Policy which explains how Layer Marney Tower uses and protects information which you provide when you enter our website. Personal data you provide will only be used to respond to an enquiry, send out a brochure or leaflet or to send you marketing information.
By accessing the Layer Marney Tower web site you consent to the collection, use and transfer of this information under the terms of this policy. Please do email info@layermarneytower.co.uk or write to Layer Marney Tower, Colchester, Essex, CO5 9US if you have any queries about the policy.
Information we collect from you
When you visit our web site and submit a query to our website you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself (“personally identifiable information”) this is so we can provide you with information about our services at Layer Marney Tower.
Browsing
We do not collect information which would personally identify you when you browse our web site. This means unless you give us personal information (such as asking for a brochure) we will not know your name, your email address or any other information about you.
Use of information
We will use the personal information which you have given us to deal with an enquiry, sending a brochure or any other information you have requested. We may store the information you have given us and use it for direct marketing or telling you about special events, special offers etc. If you do not want to us to use this information, please let us know and we will remove your name and information from our database.
Emails, special offers, promotions, special events etc.
We will only send you emails that we feel will be useful and of interest to you. We may email you with information about special offers, promotions, special events etc.
Links
The Layer Marney Tower web site contains links to other sites. Layer Marney Tower is not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of any of these sites. The policy in this statement applies only to the Layer Marney Tower website.
Copyright
The legal ownership and any copyright within the site, its design, text, graphics etc belong to Layer Marney Tower unless otherwise stated.
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.OkCookie policy
